(Bernadette:)Hey, Raj.
(Raj:)Hey, how's the mommy-to-be?
(Bernadette:)Good. A little tired.
(Raj:)I feel you. I've been
dating multiple women.
(Howard:)You sure you don't
want to come
watch Game of
Thrones with us?
(Bernadette:)You guys have fun.
(Bernadette:)I'm just gonna snuggle up
in bed with a book.
(Raj:)Oh, that sounds great...
a bed to yourself.
(Raj:)Can't even remember
what that's like.
(Sheldon:)Are you up-to-date
on Game of Thrones?
(Penny:)Mm, I think so.
(Penny:)Dragons, snow zombies,
and all the hot guys are dead.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I don't know.
(Sheldon:)Theon Greyjoy
looks pretty good
(Sheldon:)for a guy who had his
genitals cut off.
(singsongy): Uh-oh,
somebody's still pouting.
(Leonard:)Leave me alone.
(Penny:)If it's because
you lost a stick,
(Penny:)I know where it went.
(Leonard:)Not funny.
(Penny:)You know you're gonna
make up with him.
(Penny:)Can we just skip to that part?
(Leonard:)Oh, of course, because
I'm the only adult around here.
(Penny:)Really? The only adult?
(Leonard:)Yeah, that's right.
SHELDON: You know, excuse me.